

msethi437@gmail.com

+91 8800390861

New Delhi

in

linkedin.com/in/mihir--sethi/

Summary

Experienced Digital Marketer with strong skills in Media Strategy, GA4/GTM configuration, Data Visualization and Google Ads. Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy.

Certification

Growing business with Facebook Training Facebook 2022-04-28

Google Analytics Advanced Training Google 2022-07-01

Content Marketing Training Hubspot Academy 2022-08-18

Digital Marketing
Certification
UpGrad Campus 2022-10-10

Personal Projects

- Created a Word Press Website named as www.tripify.site.
- 2. Project on Search Engine
 Marketing and Search
 engine Optimization
 under the guidance of
 Ms. Mansi Anand through
 upGrad campus.
- Project on Email
 marketing and Web
 Analytics under the
 guidance of Ms. Pallavi
 through upGrad campus.

Skills

 Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel, JavaScript, Search engine optimization (SEO), Search engine marketing (SEM), Social media marketing (SMM), Facebook ads, Email Marketing, Content Marketing, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Looker studio, Cold Outreach, Creative Writing.

Experience

Digital Marketing Analytics Associate

Tradehike Consulting Oct 2022 - Present

- Strategically manage GA4/GTM setup for US and UK clients, and create Looker Studio dashboards for client insights.
- 2. Lead media planning efforts, that outline recommended media channels, budgets, and schedules to achieve campaign goals.
- 3. Optimize Google Ads campaigns for better ROI.
- 4. Manage setup and execution of core performance lead campaigns and email marketing initiatives to drive sales for the organization.

Social Media Marketing Intern

Little Hand Foundation Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

- Increased brand awareness and followers through comprehensive social media campaign management.
- Developed creative and unique campaign visuals, including videos, reels and images.

Digital Marketing Intern

Doric Multimedia Pvt Ltd Mar 2022 - May 2022

- Assisted with the development and execution of digital marketing campaigns,
- 2. Created engaging content and copy for social media posts, promotional emails and other marketing collateral.

Education

B.Tech - Electronics and Communication Engineering Dr. Akhilesh Das Gupta Institute of Technology And Management Aug 2019 - Jul 2023

CGPA - 8.9

XII

Air Force Bal Bharti School Jul 2018 - Jun 2019 Percentage - 83.3%

X
Air Force Bal Bharti School Jul 2016 - Jun 2017
CGPA - 8.8